https://www.nebh.org/privacy-statement/

Navigation follows, skip to content?
Utility navigation follows, skip to content?
Find a Doctor
Give Now
Contact Us
Search
Primary navigation follows, skip to content?
Musculoskeletal Imaging Fellowship
Orthopedic Surgery Physician Assistant Fellowship (OSPAF)
Important Information
(Click to learn more)
New England Baptist Hospital DOES NOT have an emergency department or urgent care centers.
Visitor Information | Donation Information | DPH Attestations for Phase 1, 2 and 3
Privacy Statement
At New England Baptist Hospital, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We encourage you to review our privacy policy and learn about your rights as a patient. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy statement.
New England Baptist Hospital (NEBH) is committed to protecting your privacy. The NEBH website allows you to visit most areas without identifying yourself or providing personal information. For those areas where you elect to provide identifiable information, we assure you that we make every effort to protect your privacy. In this privacy statement, we have attempted to inform you about our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
We have taken reasonable steps to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of personally identifiable information you voluntarily and explicitly provide. However, electronic transmissions via the Internet are not necessarily secure from interception and so we cannot guarantee the security or confidentiality of such transmissions.
New England Baptist Hospital routinely gathers data on website activity, such as how many people visit the site, the pages they visit, where they come from, how long they stay, etc. The data is collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, which means no personally identifiable information is associated with the data. This data helps us improve site content and overall usage. This information is not shared with other organizations. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations or other facially valid legal processes, we will not share any information we receive with any outside parties.
We and our Third Party Service Provider collect and save the default information customarily logged by worldwide web server software. Our logs contain the following information for each request: date and time, originating IP address and domain name (the unique address assigned to your Internet service provider’s computer that connects to the Internet), object requested, and completion status of the request. These logs may be kept for an indefinite amount of time, used at any time and in any way necessary to prevent security breaches and to ensure the integrity of the data on our servers.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site or your dealings with it, you can write us at:
New England Baptist Hospital
Marketing Department
125 Parker Hill Avenue
Boston, MA 02120
Footer navigation follows, return to top?
Mobile Navigation
Find a Doctor
Patients & Care Partners
Becoming a Patient
Patient Education
Financial Resources
Cost Estimates
Financial Services Guide
Musculoskeletal Imaging Fellowship
Orthopedic Surgery Physician Assistant Fellowship (OSPAF)
Research
Programs
Orthopedic Registry
Active Research Studies
Boston Sports Medicine Symposium
Thank You to Our Supporters
Nursing
Video Education Portal
Search
We use cookies and other tools to enhance your experience on our website and to analyze our web traffic. For more information about these cookies and the data collected, please refer to our web privacy statement.
